    "The act of consciousness is motivated by the presence of a third party alongside of the neighbor approached.",
    "A third party is also approached; and the relationship between the neighbor and the third party cannot be indifferent to me when I approach.",
    "To be on the ground of the signification of an approach is to be with another for or against a third party, with the other and the third party against oneself, in justice.",
    "In this disinterestedness, when, as a responsibility for the other, it is also a responsibility for the third party, the justice that compares, assembles and conceives, the synchrony of being and peace, take form.",
    "Nor is it the representation of the spatial environment, nor even the \"objective\" fact of this spatial environment observable by a third party or deducible by me, who am palpating the object, from the fact of this palpation.",
    "In proximity a subject is implicated in a way not reducible to the spatial sense which proximity takes on when the third party troubles it by demanding justice in the \"unity of transcendental consciousness,\" when a conjuncture is sketched out in a theme which, when said, is garbed with the sense of a contiguity.",
    "The representation of signification is itself born in the signifyingness of proximity in the measure that a third party is alongside the neighbor.",
    "The way by which, from this situation, the logos arises to the concept of the ego passes through the third party.",
    "The fact that the other, my neighbor, is also a third party with respect to another, who is also a neighbor, is the birth of thought, consciousness, justice and philosophy.",
    "It is in prophecy that the Infinite escapes the objectification of thematization and of dialogue, and signifies as illeity, in the third person. ",
    "This \"thirdness\" is different from that of the third man, it is the third party that interrupts the face to face of a welcome of the other man, interrupts the proximity or approach of the neighbor, it is the third man with which justice begins.",
    "It is troubled and becomes a problem when a third party enters.",
    "The third party is other than the neighbor, but also another neighbor, and also a neighbor of the other, and not simply his fellow.",
    "What then are the other and the third party for one another?",
    "The other stands in a relationship with the third party, for whom I cannot entirely answer, even if I alone answer, before any question, for my neighbor.",
    "The other and the third party, my neighbors, contemporaries of one another, put distance between me and the other and the third party.",
    "The third party introduces a contradiction in the saying whose signification before the other until then went in one direction.",
    "The entry of a third party is the very fact of consciousness, assembling into being, and at the same time, in a being, the hour of the suspension of being in possibility, the finitude of essence accessible to the abstraction of concepts, to the memory that assembles in presence, the reduction of a being to the possible and the reckoning of possibles, the comparison of incomparables. It is the thematization of the same on the basis of the relationship with the other, starting with proximity and the immediacy of saying prior to problems, whereas the identification of knowing by itself absorbs every other.",
    "It is not that the entry of a third party would be an empirical fact, and that my responsibility for the other finds itself constrained to a calculus by the \"force of things.\" ",
    "The relationship with the third party is an incessant correction of the assymetry of proximity in which the face is looked at.",
    "Consciousness is born as the presence of a third party.",
    "It is the entry of the third party, a permanent entry, into the intimacy of the face to face.",
    "And it is because the third party does not come empirically to trouble proximity, but the face is both the neighbor and the face of faces, visage and visible, that, between the order of being and of proximity the bond is unexceptionable.",
    "Order, appearing, phenom- enality, being are produced in signification, in proximity, starting with the third party.",
    "The apparition of a third party is the very origin of appearing, that is, the very origin of an origin.",
    "The extraordinary commitment of the other to the third party calls for control, a search for justice, society and the State, comparison and possession, thought and science, commerce and philosophy, and outside of anarchy, the search for a principle.",
    "Philosophy circumscribes the life of the approach and it measures obligations before the third party with justice and knowledge, with wisdom; it does not undo this life.",
    "It claimed to describe a third condition or the unconditionality of an excluded middle.",
