    "Alterity figures in it outside any qualification of the other for the ontological order and outside any attribute. It figures as what is near in a proximity that counts as sociality, which \"excites\" by its pure and simple proximity.",
    "At least the first indications of these eventualities permit us to announce the orientation of this chapter, which does not begin by running up against the finitude of the subject devoted to the relativity of a forever unfinished science. Instead, in this very finitude, taken as an outcome of the-one-for-the-other structure characteristic of proximity, we already catch sight of the excellence, the height and the signification, of responsibility, that is, of sociality, an order to which finite truth ┬ù being and consciousness - are subordinate.",
    "Absolving himself from all essence, all genus, all resemblance, the neighbor, the first one on the scene, concerns me for the first time (even if he is an old acquaintance, an old friend, an old lover, long caught up in the fabric of my social relations) in a contingency that excludes the a priori.",
    "This means concretely or empirically that justice is not a legality regulating human masses, from which a technique of social equilibrium is drawn, harmonizing antagonistic forces. That would be a justification of the State delivered over to its own necessities.",
