    "But the persisting in being, interest, is maintained by the future compensation which will have to equilibriate the concessions patiently and politically consented to in the immediate.",
    "Failing already presupposes a freedom and the imperialism of a political or ecclesiastical ego, that is, a history of constituted and free egos.",
    "The act of consciousness would thus be political simultaneousness, but also in reference to God, to a God always subject to repudiation and in permanent danger of turning into a protector of all the egoisms.",
    "It reminds us of the, in a very broad sense, political character of all logical rationalism, the alliance of logic with politics.",
